come back some day but you will
don't throw someone like this in fries
forehead on me if I'm sad or something
like that You don't know anyone like that or do
Do you feel it No no you are the best Have it
good when I looked out over the prices so
was quite expensive But as usual
say You get what you pay for and i
In this case, I got a real one
good sandwich and perhaps Sweden's tastiest
fries I have only one thing to say
beetle I saw and not a cockroach
I wouldn't be surprised if it was
the latter when the cleanliness is rounded
the serving and the garbage station were among them
It was the most disgusting thing I've seen in a long time